<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[duemir's place]]></title>
  <link href="http://duemir.net/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://duemir.net/"/>
  <updated>2013-08-05T22:01:52+10:00</updated>
  <id>http://duemir.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Denys Digtiar]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://duemir.net/blog/2013/04/18/re-blog/"/>
    <updated>2013-04-18T12:00:00+10:00</updated>
    <id>http://duemir.net/blog/2013/04/18/re-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Stuck somewhere in the back of my mind is this idea, that I for some unknown reason MUST have a blog. As if having <a href="https://twitter.com/duemir">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/duemir">Facebook</a> and <a href="https://plus.google.com/117210174858127001323/posts">Google+</a> is not enough to fulfil my sharing needs, not to mention numerous other services I am registered on, such as <a href="https://foursquare.com/user/1638511">foursquare</a>, <a href="http://instagram.com/duemir#">Instagram</a>, <a href="http://au.linkedin.com/in/denysdigtiar/">LinkedIn</a>, <a href="https://coderwall.com/duemir">Coderwall</a> and some Russian clones of previously mentioned. Not that I am using all this junk, at the moment I focus my attention only on Twitter, Instagram, foursquare and LinkedIn. Anyway, I want a blog to try to keep my knowledge organized, to express my opinions and thoughts, to share my experiences and just to own it. OK. Decided! I am doing this blogging thing!!!</p>

<p>Why re-blog than? Because I had a blog on this same URL. Nothing particularly interesting. Nothing that I could not have shared using Twitter, except maybe one post. In this incarnation of the blog I promise to be more conscious of the format and not publish single sentence posts. Therefore, I encourage you to follow me on <a href="https://twitter.com/duemir">Twitter</a> but be aware that I also use it as a medium for sharing my favourite music.</p>

<p>As a conclusion, a little bit about blog structure. I plan to categorize every post in either <strong><em>Work</em></strong> or <strong><em>Life</em></strong> category. <strong><em>Work</em></strong> is everything IT related, <strong><em>Life</em></strong> &ndash; everything else. I will use additional content specific categories but these two are mandatory. In my opinion, this way it will be easy to separate all technical from all non-technical stuff and only read or subscribe to what you are interested in. Speaking of which, links to the category pages are bellow, following are links to RSS: <strong><em><a href="http://duemir.net/blog/categories/work/atom.xml">Work</a></em></strong> and <strong><em><a href="http://duemir.net/blog/categories/life/atom.xml">Life</a></em></strong>.</p>

<p>That is it. Wait for the first post.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
